(Howard:)Okay, wait, how about this?
(Howard:)We say there were four goth girls.
(Howard:)The two girls in the club had two friends.
(Raj:)I like it, I like it.
(Raj:)Did they smell good
despite their goth-like nature?
-What's that gotta do with the story?
-Engaging my olfactory sense...
(Raj:)-...helps make it real for me.
-Fine, they smelled good.
(Raj:)Oh, they did.
Like jasmine and honeysuckle.
(Penny:)-Whatever.
-And they held hands...
(Raj:)...and did a sexy demonic hokey-pokey
for us.
No. Let me say my story all the way,
and then you can say yours...
(Howard:)-...then we'll pick.
-I'm sorry. Go on.
(Howard:)We got tattoos, and then the four girls
took us to their place.
(Raj:)We don't have tattoos. What if someone
asks to see our tattoos?
(Howard:)We say they're in a very intimate area.
(Raj:)Oh, we are bad boys, aren't we?
(Howard:)-Right. Right.
-Yeah. Ha, ha.
(Howard:)So we go back to their place,
and then the six of us end up in a hot tub.
(Raj:)But we just got tattoos. Wouldn't we be
concerned about bacterial infection?
(Howard:)True. Okay, forget the hot tub.
The point is, we each had a ménage
with sexy goth girls.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Raj:)What a great night.
(Penny:)Yeah.
Hey, wanna try a country bar
tomorrow night?
(Raj:)Yeah, maybe we'll get lucky
with sexy cowgirls.
(Howard:)-Could happen.
-Ha, ha.
(Raj:)I wonder how they smell.